Guide to the Elizabeth S. Lyman Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Additional papers, Accession ARCH-2014-100
  - Women's Funding Assistance Project, 1982 Feb 11 (Box 7, Folder 168)
  - Women's Funding Assistance Project: appointment of Judith Sutphen, 1981 May 8 (Box 7, Folder 169)
  - WAF/CP Annual Report May 1980-April 1981, 1980 May - 1981 Apr (Box 7, Folder 170)
  - WAF/CP General Organization 80-81, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 171)
  - WAF/CP Grant letters, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 172)
  - Planning Committees, 1975-1980 (Box 7, Folder 173)
  - WAF/CP Letter to board about committees, 1980 Jul (Box 7, Folder 174)
  - Women's Conference News Briefs, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 175)
  - Washington Foundation Luncheon Group Members Attending WAF/CP Luncheon, 1980 Jul (Box 7, Folder 176)
  - Business World "Women in Banking", 1980 Mar 11 (Box 7, Folder 177)
  - Letter to Potlach Corporation from Lyman, 1978 Nov 3 (Box 7, Folder 178)
  - The San Mateo Foundation: Creativity and Small Foundations, 1980 Aug (Box 7, Folder 179)
  - Planning Committees, 1975 -1980 (Box 7, Folder 180)
  - Proposal for standardized grant request form, 1983 Feb 16 (Box 7, Folder 181)
  - Note on distribution of curriculum guide, 1978 Sep 27 (Box 7, Folder 182)
  - Funding of female services in the SF Bay Area, 1979 Nov 5 (Box 7, Folder 183)
  - "Welcome to the Club" clippings: female access to male-dominated institutions, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 184)
  - WAF/CP: Challening discrimination in private clubs, 1981 Apr (Box 7, Folder 185)
  - Women in the world, 1980 Dec 23 (Box 7, Folder 186)
  - The New York Community Trust: Girls and Young Women's Status, 1981 May 7 (Box 7, Folder 187)
  - The Women's Foundation: program on lack of funding for women's and girl's programs, 1983 Aug 5 (Box 7, Folder 188)
  - The Women's Foundation correspondence, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 189)
  - WAF/CP Sixth Annual Meeting "Working Poor Women", 1983 (Box 7, Folder 190)
  - WAF/CP Funding of Programs for Women and Girls by a Selected Sample of Major Corps, 1980 May (Box 7, Folder 191)
  - Removing Financial Support from Private Clubs that Discriminate Against Women, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 192)
  - Part Time for a Lifetime: The Limitations Facing Working Women, 1982 Jul (Box 7, Folder 193)
  - Inequality of Sacrifice: The Impact of the Reagan Budget on Women, 1982 Oct (Box 7, Folder 194)
  - WAF/CP Publications, 1982 Sep 1 (Box 7, Folder 195)
  - Silicon valley Community Foundation, undated (Box 7, Folder 196)
  - Women's Health at Stanford, undated (Box 7, Folder 197)
  - The Business Journal "A passion for women's rights", 2000 May 5 (Box 7, Folder 198)
  - Card from Changemakers, 2000 Nov 20 (Box 7, Folder 199)
  - Ms. Foundation for Women The National Women's Fund Annual Report, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 200)
  - 2000 Annual Meeting Attendee List, 2000 May 18 (Box 7, Folder 201)
  - Taking Charge: How Women's Funds are Changing the Face of Philanthropy, 2000 Mar (Box 7, Folder 202)
  - Ms. Foundation 2000 Annual Report, 2001 Apr 23 (Box 7, Folder 203)
  - Ms. Foundation for Women newsletter Spring 2001 (Box 7, Folder 204)
  - First Nations Development Institute 20 Year Report, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Africa Region Microcredit Summit Meeting of Councils, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Shelterforce: The Journal of Affordable Housing and Community Building #117, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - AEO Inquiries, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - AEO 1994 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Cameo Sacramento, CA 6/12-13/08, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - CCEDA Public Policy and Funding Conference, 2000 June 12 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - CAMEO Calif Assoc. Of MicroEnt Orgs, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - CAMEO '98-99, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Start-Up (EPA) Fay Menair-knox, 1999 June (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - 04\05 Women and Philanthropy Annual Meeting, 2004-2005 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - 10/17/06 Women's Initiative, 2006 Oct 17 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - 01 YMCA of Mid-Peninsula archives, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - 2001 YMCA of Mid-Peninsula Womens Entrepreneurs Program (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - MidPen YMCA Advisory, 1999-2001 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Women's Initiative for Employment Expansion to South Bay, 2006 Feb 17 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Enterprise Community Partners 2009 Annual Meeting, 2009 Mar 27 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Board of Trustees Conflict of Interest Policy, 2009 Mar 18 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Northern California Leadership Council, 2009 Feb 24 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Enterprise, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Enterprise Community Partners Board of Trustees Meeting, 2008 Dec 10 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Letters to Feinstein and Pelosi from Lyman, 2009 Jan 27 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Jeffrey Donahue retirement plans, 2009 Jan 21 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Fax Memo from Donahue, 2009 Jan 21 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Fax Memo from Donahue about board meeting cancellation, 2009 Jan 14 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Email from Norman Rice: strategic plan document, 2009 Jan (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Enterprise Financial Review Committee, 2008 Oct 31 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Financial Review Committee Meeting Memo and Minutes, 2008 Oct (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Bid to purchase Starrett City, 2008 Jul (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Enterprise News Autumn 2008, 2008 Oct (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Enterprise Newsletters, 2008 Oct (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Enterprise presents the Gotham City Gala, 2008 Sep 29 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - 2008 Enterprise Community Conference, 2008 Oct 17 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Interview with Gryzwinski on the Community Reinvestment Act, 2008 Oct 9 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Notice of former trustee Harry Albright's passing, 2008 Oct 15 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Enterprise Board of Trustees Meeting, 2008 Sep 17 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Enterprise Financial Review Committee Meeting, 2008 Sep 11 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Letter about Bart Harvey Enterprise Fellowship recipient, 2008 Aug 13 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Fax Memo about New Generation Fund, 2008 Aug 6 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Financial Review Committee Meeting, 2008 Jun 24 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, 2008 Jun 25 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Enterprise Strategic Plan, 2009-2013 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Foreclosure-related news clips, 2008 Mar 12 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - New Orleans-related news clips, 2008 Mar 12 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Fax Memo: Thank you from Bart Harvey, 2008 Mar 14 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - 15 Years of Results: HUD Section 4 Program Leverages Local Success, undated (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Jing Lyman Executive Committee, 2008 Mar (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Fax Memo: Dinner choices, 2008 Mar 7 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Note on flights, 2008 Feb 8 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting and Committee Meetings, 2008 Mar 11-12 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Membership card for National Museum of Women in the Arts, 2008-2009 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - NYT article "The Right Answer in New Orleans", 2007 Dec 25 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Resource Development Committee Notes and Agenda, 2008 Mar 3 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Financial Review Committee Meeting Agenda, 2008 Mar 5 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Enterprise Board of Trustees Meeting, 2008 Mar 12 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Fax Memo: Bill Frey honored by Phipps Housing, 2007 Sep 19 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Giving in the Aftermath of the Gulf Coast Hurricanes, 2007 Aug (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, 2007 Sep 12 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Enterprise Board of Trustees Conflict of Interest Policy, 2007 Sep (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Financial Review Committee Meeting, 2007 Sep 12 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - FedEx Package from Enterprise Community Partners to Lyman, 2006 Jun (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Apple Mousepad, undated (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 2003 Jun 18 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Combined meeting of the executive committee and the financial review committee, 2003 Jun 17 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Combined financial statements and independent auditors' report, 2001-2002 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Enterprise Foundation folder, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - California Association for Micro Enterprise Opportunity, 2010 (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Board Elections Ballot CAMEO, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - CAMEO Looking Forward Annual Report, 2007 (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - CAMEO membership renewal, 2008 Feb 14 (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - CAMEO Member Directory, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - Ballot for CAMEO board elections, 2007 (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Postcard on events, undated (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - CAMEO purpose and goals, 2007 Oct 16 (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - CAMEO Developing Latino Entrepreneurs, 2007 Oct 16-17 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Board Candidate Biographies, 2007-2008 (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Annual Meeting and Salsa Reception, 2007 Sep 12 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Microenterprise Development in Action, 2005 Sep 12 (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Enterprising Times Newsletter, 2004 Jul (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - CAMEO Guidebook to California Microenterprise Development, 2004 Apr 9 (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - CAMEO membership renewal, 2003 Nov 14 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Microenterpise. It's bigger than you think., undated (Box 8, Folder 82)
  - CAMEO fundraising, 2002 Sep 30 (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - Enterprising Times Newsletter Summer 2002 (Box 8, Folder 84)
  - 2002 CAMEO Member Resource Directory (Box 8, Folder 85)
  - CAMEO annual meeting, 2003 Feb 28 (Box 8, Folder 86)
  - CAMEO Membership Directory Update, 2003 Apr 18 (Box 8, Folder 87)
  - CAMEO membership renewal, 2000 Dec 23 (Box 8, Folder 88)
  - Enterprising Times newsletter Fall 2000 (Box 8, Folder 89)
  - Enterprising Times AEO special edition, 2001 Jul 20 (Box 8, Folder 90)
  - CAMEO Membership Directory Update, 2001 Mar (Box 8, Folder 91)
  - CAMEO microenterprise development for your client, your community, and California, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 92)
  - Channing House, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 93)
  - Channing house, 2006-2008 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Channing house, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 2)